studentloan.org 2008-05-16

# Online Privacy Statement - Iowa Student Loan - Picture Your Success!

We understand that you are concerned about the privacy and security of your personal information. This Online Privacy Statement describes the ways we may collect and use information we obtain from you online when you visit a Web site provided by Iowa Student Loan Liquidity Corporation. The amount, type and use of the information we receive depend on how you use this Web site. Your activities on our Web site may also be governed by our Customer Privacy Notice that describes how we collect, use and retain consumer information that you may provide to us. 

## Effective Date

This Online Privacy Statement is effective as of April 26, 2007. 

## Changes to the Privacy Statement

We may change this Privacy Statement at any time. Any changes will be effective after we post them to this Web site. We recommend that you check back periodically to review it. 

## Information We Collect and Why

### Personal Information

We collect personal information that you voluntarily provide us through electronic mail, electronic Web site forms and other electronic means. “Personal Information” means information that can specifically identify a person, such as your name, phone number, address, e-mail address, date of birth, income, account number, driver’s license number and social security number. Our Web server automatically collects information that includes, without limitation, information about your Internet service provider, the Web sites from which you connect to our Web sites, the browser you use and the pages that you access on our site (“Web Site Use Information”). We compile and sort this information in order to develop group profiles of our Web site visitors, to assist with systems administration and to resolve problems. 

### Use of Cookies

We use cookies to collect information. A cookie is a computer file that your Web browser saves to your computer’s hard drive to store information about your use of this Web site. Our collection of Web Site Use Information may involve the use of “session cookies.” Session cookies are temporary and are deleted after you close your Web browser. Session cookies do not collect personally identifying information from your computer. Among other uses, session cookies allow us to deliver content specific to your interests and to improve Web site navigation. In some instances, we obtain authentication information by the use of “persistent” cookies. We use persistent cookies for customer protection, as part of our authentication technology. Persistent cookies assist us in verifying the identity of a customer who is attempting to log in to an account. 

You may block the use of cookies by changing the settings on your Web browser or by using a software program that blocks cookies. If you choose to block cookies, the Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers can instruct you how to configure your Web browser to accept cookies, not to accept new cookies, to notify you when you receive a new cookie or to disable cookies altogether. However, if you choose to block cookies, you may not be able to access some features of our Web site application. 

### Use of Personal Information

We use Personal Information for purposes that include – without limitation – processing loan applications, administering loan accounts, providing services to customers, providing Web site visitors or customers with information about our products, services and upcoming events, and complying with legal or regulatory requirements. 

### Disclosing Personal Information

We do not share Personal Information except as permitted by law. We disclose Personal Information to our family of companies and other companies and individuals that we employ to perform functions on our behalf under confidentiality agreements. They may perform functions including, but not limited to, analyzing data, supplying marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), fulfilling orders, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists and providing customer service. We expect the companies we select as our business partners and service providers to honor our Customer Privacy Notice when they handle information about our customers. We do not sell or rent our customer information to any outside company or organization. 

We disclose account and other Personal Information as permitted by law when we believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the legal process or assist law enforcement authorities; enforce our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property or safety of our users or others. This type of disclosure includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

### Internal Marketing

If you supply us with your electronic mail address, postal address and/or telephone number online, we may contact you or send you information about our new products, services or upcoming events. If you do not want to receive information about available products and services or upcoming events, you may send us an electronic message at [privacy@studentloan.org](mailto:privacy@studentloan.org) or advise us during any telephone call we have with you. Please provide us with your exact name and address. If possible, provide us with your name as it appears on any mailings you have received from our family of companies. 

### Security

We protect your Personal Information by maintaining administrative and technical safeguards that meet or exceed applicable law. We train our employees in the proper handling of Personal Information. When we use other companies to provide services for us, we require them to protect the confidentiality of any Personal Information they may receive. We combine these technical safeguards with physical safeguards and employee policies to further protect your information. 

### Children’s Privacy

We do not knowingly collect, maintain or use personal information from our Web sites about children under age 13. If we learn that we have collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will promptly take all reasonable steps to delete the information. 

### Linked Sites

This Web site may display links to Web sites of other companies. If you link to a site that is not an Iowa Student Loan Web site, the privacy policy of that site applies to you. We are not responsible for the way that site may collect, use disclose or secure the personal information that you provide to them. Please read their privacy policy to learn how they use your personal information. 

## Contact Information

If you have questions about this Online Privacy Statement, please contact:  
Privacy Department   
Iowa Student Loan   
P.O. Box 7311   
Des Moines, IA 50309-7311   
(800) 507-3814 or [privacy@studentloan.org](mailto:privacy@studentloan.org)

## CUSTOMER PRIVACY NOTICE  
Iowa Student Loan Liquidity Corporation®

### Protecting your Privacy

This Customer Privacy Notice describes how Iowa Student Loan Liquidity Corporation (“we,” “us” and “our”) may collect and disclose personal information about our customers. 

### How we Collect Information

We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources: 

  * Information we receive from you on applications or other forms. 
  * Information about your transactions with us or others. 
  * Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency. 
  * Information we receive from nonaffiliated third parties, such as your school and any guarantor of your loan.

### How we Share Information

We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about current or former customers to anyone, except as permitted by law. For example, we are permitted to share nonpublic personal information about you with nonaffiliated third parties in the following ways: 

  * To consumer reporting agencies. 
  * To companies that provide services for us, such as data processing companies or collection agencies. 
  * To service or process a financial product or service you request. 
  * Protecting you or us against potential fraud, identity theft or unauthorized transactions. 
  * To provide information required or permitted for legal, transactional or regulatory purposes. 
  * When we are legally required to do so, such as responding to subpoenas or court orders. 
  * With your consent or at your direction. 

We may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf. We may also disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to other financial institutions with which we have joint marketing agreements unless our records show that your primary address is in California or Vermont. 

### Special Notice for California and Vermont Residents

If our records show that your primary address is in California or Vermont, we will not disclose nonpublic personal information about you to other financial institutions with which we have a joint marketing agreement, except as permitted by law. 

### Confidentiality and Security

We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your nonpublic personal information. 

### More Information

If you have questions about our Customer Privacy Notice or our privacy practices, you may contact us by sending an e-mail addressed to: [privacy@studentloan.org](mailto:privacy@studentloan.org); calling toll-free at (800) 507-3814; or sending correspondence addressed to: Iowa Student Loan, Attn: Privacy Officer, P.O. Box 7311, Des Moines, IA 50309-7311. We may make changes to this Customer Privacy Notice at any time, and will inform you of any changes. This Customer Privacy Notice is effective as of April 26, 2007.
